<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes" ?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Abouts on sammler.io Documentation</title>
    <link>https://sammler.github.io/docs/about/</link>
    <description>Recent content in Abouts on sammler.io Documentation</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language>
    <copyright>Released under the MIT license</copyright>
    
	<atom:link href="https://sammler.github.io/docs/about/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    
    
    <item>
      <title>About sammler.io</title>
      <link>https://sammler.github.io/docs/about/00-about/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sammler.github.io/docs/about/00-about/</guid>
      <description>Introduction sammler is my very personal attempt to bring business life, social activities and IoT together.
I am fully adopting cloud computing as consumer and producer, but I hate it, that I don&amp;rsquo;t have all the data available at a fingertip - just to be able to analyze them.
Furthermore I am fully adopting IoT, collecting already more than 1GB each week.
So I need a solution to constantly collect and analyze all the data, their correlation, just to get interesting insights.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Principles</title>
      <link>https://sammler.github.io/docs/about/15-principles/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sammler.github.io/docs/about/15-principles/</guid>
      <description>While working on sammler I have defined some principles, I try to follow:
 Everything is open sourced. Follow a Readme Driven Development.  Publish everything: my progress, failure, thoughts, decisions.
(Will be fun in a year from now to especially read all the silly decisions ;-))  Use as much existing solutions as possible, focus on assembling, rather than writing new code. All activities should be continuously tested and deployed to the cloud.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technology Choices</title>
      <link>https://sammler.github.io/docs/about/technology-choices/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sammler.github.io/docs/about/technology-choices/</guid>
      <description>Some opinionated assumptions and technology choices have been made. But this might change over time.
 Programming/scripting languages: JavaScript / TypeScript, GoLang UI framework: Angular + TypeScript CSS framework: Clarity Storage: MongoDB Messaging: RabbitMQ Containerization: Docker Service orchestration: Docker Swarm, Kubernetes Deployment: Packer, Terraform, Vagrant  All other decisions will be documented over time.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Roadmap</title>
      <link>https://sammler.github.io/docs/about/roadmap/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sammler.github.io/docs/about/roadmap/</guid>
      <description>I have spent most of 2017 to get some of the basics done for sammler (and basically learn, learn &amp;amp; learn). Now it&amp;rsquo;s time to bring everything together.
Therefore phases have been defined for the next development steps.
Phase 1: Core Have some scheduled tasks defined (file based, just a YML file) (=jobs) in the scheduler-service Run those scheduled tasks, publishing messages to RabbitMQ Periodically listening to the tasks and executing (heartbeat-service) Writing the results to a log-service (strategy-heartbeat) Show the results of the log-service in a UI heartbeat-service-ui Log both locally or using a LaaS provider  Show the log results in some basic UI  Phase 2: Runnable Stack scheduler-service with predefined jobs (.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>FAQ</title>
      <link>https://sammler.github.io/docs/about/faq/</link>
      <pubDate>Mon, 01 Jan 0001 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate>
      
      <guid>https://sammler.github.io/docs/about/faq/</guid>
      <description>What does sammler mean? sammler is the german word for collector, gatherer, assembler or collecting agent.
How is the name written? sammler, not Sammler.
What&amp;rsquo;s s5r ? s5r is just the abbreviation for sammler, just being lazy and because it looks cool and unique ;-)</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>